我们的下一个原则是用好名字
Our next principle is using good names
用于方法、变量和类。
for your methods, variables, and classes.
最好的名字是长的，而且是自我描述的。
Best names are long and self-descriptive.
事实上，如果你有好名字，你
In fact if you have good names, you
通常可以完全避免写评论
can often avoid writing a comment entirely
因为名称、方法和变量
because the names and the methods and variables
你用的是说出代码的作用。
you are using say what the code does.
这里有一个坏方法的例子。
So here's an example of a bad way to do it.
变量名为temp。
The variable is named temp.
所以你必须用评论来描述它
And so you have to describe it with a comment explaining
它的作用。
what it does.
最好给它起个名字
Much, much better would be to give it a name that actually
描述它的功能。
describes what it does.
因为这不仅更短，
Because not only is this shorter,
但这意味着这个变量在任何地方都会发生
but it means that everywhere this variable occurs
在剩下的代码中，会很清楚
in the rest of the code, it will be clear
它应该代表什么。
what it's supposed to represent.
如果你只是发表评论，
Whereas if you're just putting in a comment,
你要依靠程序员
you're depending on the programmer
注意并记住这条评论。
to notice this comment and memorize it.
一般来说，这类名称TEMP，TempData，
In general, these kinds of names TEMP, TempData,
它们只是懒惰的症状。
they're just symptoms of laziness.
每个程序，每个变量都是临时的。
Every program, every variable is temporary.
每个变量都有数据。
Every variable has data in it.
所以这些名字基本上
So these kinds of names are basically
一个人没有意义。
meaningless by themselves.
你应该使用更长，更具描述性的名字
You should aim to use longer, more descriptive names so
你的代码能自己读清楚。
that your code reads clearly all by itself.
命名的一部分是确保
Part of naming is making sure that you're
遵循编程语言的惯例
following the conventions of the programming language
你在用的。
that you're using.
所以在Python中，您可能已经注意到类通常是
So in Python you may have noticed classes typically
以大写字母开头。
start with a capital letter.
变量通常都是小写的。
Variables are typically all lowercase.
当你在一个名字里有多个词的时候，
And when you have multiple words in a name,
在Python中，您要做的是用下划线分隔它们。
in Python what you do is you separate them by underscores.
在Java中，情况有点不同。
In Java things are a little bit different.
所以我们不用下划线
So instead of using underscores, we
使用camelCase，这意味着每个单词的第一个字母
use camelCase, which means that the first letter of each word
是大写的。
is capitalized.
我们仍然采用小写方法。
We still lower case methods.
我们还降低了大小写变量，
And we still lower case variables,
就像你在Python中做的那样。
just as you did in Python.
当您有一个常量时，Java中的标准
When you have a constant, the standard in Java
就是把所有的大写字母都写进去。
is to put in all capital letters.
骆驼壳不起作用，
And there camelCase doesn't work,
所以你必须用下划线把单词分开
so you have to separate the words in it with an underscore
相反。
instead.
类仍然是大写的，尽管有camelCase。
Classes are still capitalized, although with camelCase.
当我们谈到包的时候，包是小写的
And when we talk about packages, packages are in lowercase
它们被点隔开。
and they're separated by dots.
最好让你的方法命名为动词短语，
It's good to make your method names verb phrases,
像是什么？获取数据？]是大写的。
things like [? getdata ?] is upper case.
变量和类名通常是名词。
Variable and class names are typically nouns.
你要选择简短的词，要简洁。
You want to choose short words and be concise.
但要避免缩写。
But avoid abbreviations.
所以没有理由在
So there's no reason to type msg when
信息也同样清晰。
message would be just as clear.
同时也要记住一些开发人员
Also keep in mind that some of the developers who
和你一起工作可能不是以英语为母语，
work with you may not be native English speakers,
所以缩写可能更难理解。
so abbreviations may be even harder for them to understand.
所以我们一直在研究的这种[听不见的]跳跃方法
So this [INAUDIBLE] leap method that we've been working on
里面有一些坏名字，方法，参数，
has a few bad names in it, the method, parameter,
局部变量。
the local variable.
你怎么称呼他们呢？
What would you call them instead?
让我们在下面的练习中看看。
Let's look at it in the exercises next.